1, 2 heat is on
Own it, burn it, kick it, flip that
3, 4 BABYMON
We gon' get this party started
Walk in, stomping like we own the place
Trust me, I'm not just a pretty face
Yeah, I know we're seven but we ate
We gon' get this party started
Know we got the style, we got the taste
Sweet and sour lemons, lemonade
Yeah, I know we're seven but we ate
Better run that, run that
Oh my, oh my, my 지금 이 순간
Oh my, oh my, my Let it hypnotize
Loosen up, watch me set the mood
Burn it up, do it like I do
Lose your mi-mi-mind Play the music Let's 춤
리듬을 삼켜 보자 춤
We turn it up, let's party
월, 화, 수, 목, 금, 토 모두 다 함께 취해 보자 춤
춤, 춤, 춤, 춤, 춤
We wanna ride this vibe
Get out the way like, Vroom, vroom
We only got tonight
You better dance like, 춤, 춤
Baby, check my style Check me out, This that bling blow
Can't stop now Gotta keep it me like that, bow down
보여주마 나의 춤, 춤, 춤
ASA be killing it, killing it woah
We don’t stop, top billing it, billing the show
Big flex
ain’t no up next
모두가 찍 소리 못하는 Groove
Like yes, I’m the empress
이 구역에 난 I’m a MONSTER queen
Oh my oh my my
지금 이 순간
Let it hypnotize
Loosen up, watch me set the mood
Burn it up, do it like I do
Lose your muh-muh-mind, play the music
Let’s choom
리듬을 삼켜 보자 Choom
(Watch out watch out)
We turn it up, let’s party
월 화 수 목 금 토 모두 다 함께 취해 보자 Choom
(Watch out watch out)
Choom choom choom choom choom
We wanna ride this vibe
Get out the way like vroom vroom
We only got tonight
You better dance like choom choom
어둠이 짙게 내리고
이제 MONSTER party
No time to waste (Na na na)
Let’s celebrate (Na na na)
Baby 너와 나의 시간
Choom choom choom choom
That’s right
Everybody everybody make some room
Choom, that’s right
Choom choom choom choom choom
That’s right
Everybody everybody make some room
Choom, that’s right
Choom choom choom choom choom